inbox2cash.com 2017-06-23

# Privacy Policy - Inbox 2 Cash

  | 

### Privacy policy

When you use our website, you trust us with your information.

Below is our privacy policy regarding the use of that information.  
  
### Inbox 2 Cash's Privacy Policy

#### Information we gather

The following information may be gathered from our website visitors:  
IP address and user agent (browser).

#### How we use the information we gather

We use the information to enhance your visitor experience and to keep track of our website activities, specially for internal analysis.

#### The people that are given access to this information

Your personal information is only accessible by the Inbox 2 Cash administrator(s).

#### The security measures we have in place to protect your personal information

To safeguard your personal information, we keep all collected data at our secure database center.

#### Our use of cookies

Our website makes use of cookies which are small digital files that are stored in your web browser that enable us to track your return visits to our website.

Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, but we recommend you have them enabled to help us personalise your experience of our website.

Additionally, 3rd party advertisers on our site may use cookies for tracking purposes.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to sites they visit on the Internet.

Website visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
